[PING] If I were hard on you,
it was only because
I wanted you to learn.
Here.
Give it to our lawyer,
in exchange for what you've
taken from the company.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TOTO] Ping, don't tell me
this is your savings.
You might end up
with nothing left.
[PING] What matters is we make
right the things you've done.
You don't need to do this, Ping.
You know, Toto,
you're my only family left.
I don't want you
to get harmed.
Also, I'm here to tell you...
...that I'm bringing you back
to the company.
But...
...there is a condition.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll do anything, Ping.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Okay, first of all,
you need to get counseling
so that you don't fall deeper
into gambling.
And I'm going to give you
a different role
where you won't have
to handle money.
I'm also going to cut
your monthly salary
so that you can pay off
the ten million.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Thank you, Ping.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TAPPING GENTLY]
You're welcome.
We'll get through this.
Just promise that
you'll help yourself, okay?
Have some snacks first.
You're probably hungry.
Thank you.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TOTO] Ping, I'll be
your best man, okay?
[SCOFFS LIGHTLY]
You're silly.
Donato wanted us to get married
so that someone could watch
his business.
[TOTO]
So It's just a business deal?
[PING] It started that way.
But I hope...
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
I hope it becomes real
for her.
Because it's already real
for me.
[TENDER MUSIC PLAYING]
[TOTO] Ping, I know that I've
broken your trust many times.
So, my brother,
I hope this time...
...you trust what
your heart tells you.
Fight for it.
[TOTO]
I've ruined my brother's name.
I've done my part.
Now, pay off off my debt
to the company
and make sure
I don't end up in prison.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[TOTO] Listen, Ping...
Keep your eyes open, okay?
There are snakes out there,
ready to strike.
Who?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]